<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.cloveretl.gui"
      label="CloverETL Designer"
      version="3.3.0.090M2"
      provider-name="Javlin a.s."
      image="cloveretl.gif">
   <install-handler/>

   <description url="http://www.cloveretl.org/">
CloverETL Designer - Visual designer of CloverETL data transformations.
(C) Javlin, a.s.

CloverETL Designer is visual designer of data transformations which
are executed by CloverETL Engine. The CloverETL Designer has been developed
as an Eclipse platform plugin and is well integrated with other
Eclipse functionality.
   </description>

   <copyright>
CloverETL Designer
(C) Javlin, a.s.
   </copyright>

   <license url="license.html">
      CloverETL Designer Commercial License
JAVLIN Licensing Agreement
Document number: JLA060822

This is a Licensing Agreement between you, the end user of software, and Javlin, a.s. ("JAVLIN") registered in the Czech Republic.  Please read this document carefully.  If you do not agree with the following terms and conditions, immediately stop using this software!

1. Grant. JAVLIN, subject to the terms and conditions of this Licensing Agreement, hereby grants you a nonexclusive, nontransferable right and license during the term of this Licensing Agreement to use software by JAVLIN for as long as you abide by the provisions stipulated herein. The term of your license is based on the licensing fee paid based on the then-current price list of JAVLIN. The software may include functionality that will render it inoperational upon expiration of your license.

2. Copyright. The software specified in this Licensing Agreement is, and will be the sole property of JAVLIN. It is subject to copyright protection and as such, is protected to the fullest extent allowable by law. Any copy of the software you are allowed to make pursuant to this Licensing Agreement must contain the entire copyright and other notices included with the original copy of the software.

3.  Use Limitations.  Materials encompassing any software code, including programs, tools, utilities, files and otherwise, and accompanying software (collectively, "Software") are the copyrighted and patented work of Javlin a.s.  Use of such Software is governed by the terms of the licensing agreement that accompanies or is included with the Software, or by the licensing agreement expressly stated on the website page(s) accompanying the Software. Terms and licenses may only be posted with the Software downloads or at the website page where the Software can be accessed. You will not be able to use, download or install any Software that is accompanied by or includes a licensing agreement unless you agree to the terms of such licensing agreement. Absent a licensing agreement that accompanies the Software, use of the Software will be governed by the Terms of Use. YOU AGREE THAT YOU WILL NOT DECOMPILE, REVERSE ENGINEER OR OTHERWISE ATTEMPT TO DISCOVER THE SOURCE CODE OF THE SOFTWARE.  The Software is made available solely in accordance with the license agreement. Without limiting the foregoing, unless the accompanying license agreement expressly allows otherwise, any copying or redistribution of the Software is prohibited, including any copying or reproduction of the Software to any other server or location for further reproduction, redistribution or use on a service bureau basis. Any unauthorized use, copying or distribution of the Software is expressly prohibited by law, and may result in severe civil and criminal penalties. Violators will be prosecuted to the maximum extent possible. Any Software which is downloaded from or made available via the Site for or on behalf of the United States of America, its agencies and/or instrumentalities ("U.S. Government"), is provided with Restricted Rights. Use, duplication, or disclosure by the U.S. Government is subject to restrictions as set forth in subparagraph (c)(1)(ii) of the Rights in Technical Data and Computer Software clause at DFARS 252.227-7013 or subparagraphs (c)(1) and (2) of the Commercial Computer Software - Restricted Rights at 48 CFR 52.227-19, as applicable. Manufacturer is Javlin a.s., Czech Republic.

4. Transferability. This license is granted to you only and as such does not permit you to sell, lend, assign, lease or transfer in any other way any copy of the software. Any transfer in violation of this provision is not permitted and may cause your license to be terminated with no refund of the licensing fee paid.

5. Multiple License Installation. Each installation of the software purchased may be installed on one computer only. When purchasing a multiple license, the number of installations allowed is defined by the type of the license.

6. Limited Warranty. JAVLIN guarantees that the software will correspond in general terms to the description given in the user documentation for 60 days from the date the product was purchased. JAVLIN does not warrant that the software will operate without interruptions or be error-free. The warranty stated above is the only warranty given and replaces all other warranties, regardless of whether express or implied, including implied warranties of commercial aptitude and fitness for a specific purpose. In case you make a warranty claim within the 60-day warranty period, the liability of JAVLIN is limited to replacing the product or refunding you the licensing fee paid.  To be eligible to a refund, all copies of the software stored on your hard disk or otherwise archived must be destroyed, the software must be uninstalled, and the original package must be returned. Terminating a license will cause the software to be blocked to prevent subsequent use.

7.  LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.  IN NO EVENT SHALL JAVLIN, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, PARTNERS OR SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR LOSSES OF ANY KIND, OR ANY DAMAGES OR LOSSES WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING THOSE RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER OR NOT FORESEEABLE OR IF JAVLIN HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES OR LOSSES, AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, INCLUDING BREACH OF CONTRACT OR WARRANTY, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, OR ANY OTHER CLAIM ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH: (1) THE ACCESS OR USE OF OR THE INABILITY TO ACCESS OR USE THE SITE, SERVICES, OR MATERIALS; (2) THE STATEMENTS OR ACTIONS OF ANY THIRD PARTY ON OR VIA THE SITE, SERVICES OR MATERIALS; (3) ANY DEALINGS WITH VENDORS OR OTHER THIRD PARTIES; (4) ANY UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR ALTERATION OF YOUR TRANSMISSIONS, USER MATERIALS OR OTHER DATA; (5) ANY INFORMATION THAT IS SENT OR RECEIVED OR NOT SENT OR RECEIVED; (6) ANY FAILURE TO STORE OR LOSS OF DATA, FILES, MATERIALS OR OTHER CONTENT; (7) ANY SERVICES AVAILABLE THAT ARE DELAYED OR INTERRUPTED; (8) ANY WEB SITE REFERENCED OR LINKED TO FROM THIS SITE; OR (9) YOUR ACCESS TO OR USE OF OR INABILITY TO ACCESS OR USE ANY LINKED SITE.  Acceptance of the software under this agreement, you agree that JAVLIN's liability for damages caused by the use or inability to use this software is governed by the Business Code of the Czech Republic. The software is not designed for high-risk applications including situations where the failure of such software would threaten lives or cause extensive material damages. Such applications include operating parts of nuclear power plants, weapon systems, equipment designed for sustaining people's basic bodily functions, etc.

8. Responsibility for Software Updates. In order to ensure that the software functions properly, JAVLIN publishes updates to this software on its web pages. These updates improve the workings of the software, remove any bugs or keep current software's interfaces. The user is responsible for proper configuration of the software and updating process to provide for the highest possible level of functional reliability.

9. Restriction and termination of use.   JAVLIN may block, restrict, disable, suspend or terminate your access to all or part of the website, services and materials at any time in JAVLIN's sole discretion, without prior notice or liability to you.

10. Governing Law, Arbitration Clause. This Agreement shall be governed by the laws of the Czech Republic excluding conflicts of laws principles. All disputes arising under this Agreement or in connection therewith will be adjudicated by the Czech Republic Chamber of Commerce and Agrarian Chamber Arbitration Court in Prague by three arbiters appointed pursuant to the rules of the said court. Jurisdiction of general courts is excluded and all decisions are final. The contracting parties agree to comply with the decision of the arbitration court in the time specified.

Copyright (c) 2002-2012, Javlin, a.s.
info@cloveretl.com
www.cloveretl.com 
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="http://designer.cloveretl.com/update" url="http://designer.cloveretl.com/update"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.editors"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.workbench.texteditor"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.help"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.gef"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.views"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.launching"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.debug"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.debug.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.console"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.filesystem"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="com.cloveretl.gui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.3.0.090M2"/>


   <plugin
         id="com.cloveretl.gui.ddl2clover"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.3.0.090M2"
         unpack="false"/>
   <plugin
         id="com.cloveretl.gui.jmx"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.3.0.090M2"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.cloveretl.gui.cheatsheet"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.3.0.090M2"
         unpack="false"/>
</feature>
